Guide to the Peter Gardner collection, 1959-1966 MS 779
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: KRBE - "The Sampler"
  - The Sampler - Davy Jones, Sharon Steenberger, Guy Clark, 1965-05-03; Gardner_Sampler_5
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Instrumental opening; Davy Jones - "Brave Bobbie Campbell," "Solid Gone Blues"; Sharon Steenberger - "Venezuela," "The Darby Ram"; Davy Jones - "False Knight Upon the Road"; Sharon Steenberger - "My Love Doesn't Love Me at All"; Davy Jones - "When I Was Young"; Guy Clark - instrumental closing
  - The Sampler - Howie Porper, Peter Gardner, 1965-05-10; 1965-05-19; Gardner_Sampler_6
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Instrumental opening - Knob Lick Upper 10,000; Howie Porper - "Poor Wayfarin' Stranger," "Greensleeves"; Peter Gardner - "Never Go A-Rushin'," "I Gave My Love an Apple"; Howie Porper - "John B.," "Mi Caballo"; Peter Gardner - "Ca' the Yowes," "The Golden Vanity"; instrumental closing
  - The Sampler - Dick Mitchell and Amy Goodenough, 1965-05-17; 1965-05-26; Gardner_Sampler_7
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Instrumental opening; Dick Mitchell - "Railroad Bill," "Stackolee"; Amy Goodenough - "The Grey Cook," "Lucky Joe"; Dick Mitchell - "I'm a Rambler," "How Long Blues"; Amy Goodenough - "Cotton Mill Girls," "Pretty Polly"; Dick Mitchell and others - unclear if part of the show
  - The Sampler - John A. Lomax, Jr., 1965-05-24; 1965-06-01; Gardner_Sampler_8
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Peter Gardner - opening; John A. Lomax, Jr. - remarks, "No More Cane on This Brazos," "Come a Ti Yi Youpee" (2 versions), "Adies Got a Gold Mine," "Weevily Wheat," "Take This Hammer," "Sloop John B.," "Yellow Gal," "Roseanna"; Peter Gardner - closing
  - The Sampler - Guy Clark, Sarah Wiggins, Carolyn Terry, Mack Wilson, Pete Wheeler, Gary White, 1965-05-31; Gardner_Sampler_9
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Peter Gardner - opening; Guy Clark - "Tell Old Bill" - Peter Gardner explains that Clark is starting to learn to luthier; Sarah Wiggins - "Golden Apples of the Sun"; Carolyn Terry - "One Grain of Sand"; Mack Wilson and Peter Gardner - "Billy's Land," "Me Wanna Go Home"; Pete Wheeler - "Housewife's Lament"; Gary White - "Yellow Dog Blues"
  - The Sampler - The Moonshiners, 1965-06-07; 1965-06-16; Gardner_Sampler_10
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. The Moonshiners - Instrumental opening, "Banks of the Ohio," "I Wonder How the Old Folks Are at Home," "Rueben James," "Mary Deara," "Old Rattler," "Flower Bloomed in the Wildwood," "Salty Dog Blues," instrumental closing. Musicians: Robbie Shipley, Bill Northcutt, Bill Bailey, Bill Bonner
  - The Sampler - Guy Clark, Pete Wheeler, Carolyn Terry, Gary White, Peter Childs, Ballet Folklorico, 1965-06-14; 1965-06-23; Gardner_Sampler_11
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Guy Clark - "Early Morning Rain"; Pete Wheeler - "Blantyre Mine Explosion"; Carolyn Terry - "Feeling Good"; Gary White - "Little Margaret"; Peter Childs - "Jones"; Ballet Folklorico: Pedro Munoz, Horatio Bigurra, Fernando Rojas - "Albur de Amor," "Desden," "Adios"
  - The Sampler - Kathy Rote, Sarah Wiggins, Frank Davis, 1965-06-21; 1965-06-30; Gardner_Sampler_12
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Kathy Rote - "Dear Companion," "Duncan and Brady," "When I Was in My Prime"; Kathy Rote and Sarah Wiggins - "My Home's Across Smokey Mountains"; Sarah Wiggins - "Make a Long time Man Feel Bad"; Frank Davis - "Keep Your Hands Off," "Old Riley," "Jean Harlow"
  - The Sampler - John Carrick, Sarah Wiggins, Carl Snyder, 1965-06-28; 1965-07-07; Gardner_Sampler_13
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. John Carrick - "Sand Mountain Blues," "Little Girl of Hiroshima," "Trilogy - Mary Ann, Drifter, Some Wounds to Bind"; Sarah Wiggins - "Black Girl," "Cotton Eyed Joe," "Last Thing on My Mind"; Carl Snyder - "Gilgarra Mountain," "God Bless the Child," "Some Day Soon"; John Carrick - "Black Fly," "Universal Soldier"; Sarah Wiggins and Peter Gardner - "Who's Gonna Shoe"; Sarah Wiggins - "Portland Town"; Carl Snyder - "Good and Drunk and Goozy," "Down in the Mines"
  - The Sampler - Danny Schacht, Amy Goodenough, David Bayles, Peter Mann, Gary White, Carolyn Terry, Guy Clark, Segle Fry, Kathy Rote, 1965-07-05; 1965-07-14; Gardner_Sampler_14
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Danny Schacht - "Do Re Me," "She Moves Along Like a Cannonball," "Got My Questionnaire," "Golden Vanity"; Amy Goodenough - "Dewie Dens of Yorrow," "If It Fits Your Fancy," "New Shoes Blues," "I Love My Baby"; David Bayles and Peter Mann - "Cripple Creek," "Ginger Man," David Bayles and Peter Mann with Danny Schacht - "Blues"; Danny Schacht, Gary White, Carolyn Terry - "Run Sinner Run"; Carolyn Terry - "She's Like a Swallow"; Guy Clark - "Every Day Dirt"; pre-recorded performance by Segle Fry - "Salty Dog," "Come All You Fair," "Make Me a Pallet"; Kathy Rote - "Cotton Mill Girls"
  - The Sampler - Bill Palmer, Guy Clark, Jim Womack, John A. Lomax, Jr., 1965-07-19; 1965-07-28; Gardner_Sampler_15
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. In introduction by Peter Gardner mentions that Guy Clark just finished working on his 12-string. He also plans on opening up the business Clark Harmonies. Bill Palmer - "Bugle Call Rag," "Worried Man Blues," "Reuben," "Spanish Fandango," "Green Corn"; Guy Clark - "Stealin'," "Backwater Blues," "Red Velvet," "New Franking and Johnny"; Bill Palmer - "Freigh Train," "Nobody Knows You," "Nine Pound Hammer"; Jim Womack - By the Side of a Railroad," "Atomic Power," "Walked the Streets," "Crowded"; John A. Lomax, Jr. - "Silver Jack," "Jesse James"
  - The Sampler - Carl Snyder, Robin Rinker, Jeff Giles, Gary White, Paul Johnson, Amy Goodenough, 1965-07-21; Gardner_Sampler_16
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Group sing-along - "It's a Lesson Too Late for the Learning"; Carl Snyder - "Henry"; Robin Rinker - Spanish song, "Pussy Cat, Pussy Cat"; Jeff Giles on a homemade guitar - Blues progression; Gary White - Song with banjo, "Push Boat," "Fi-Li-Mi-Oo-Re-Ay"; Paul Johnson and Amy Goodenough - "Turtledove"; Gary White - "One Grain of Sand"; Amy Goodenough - "Come In, Come In"; Independence Day play
  - The Sampler - John Pollack, Tommy Thompson, Earl Palmer, Roger Abrahams, Jim Gunn, 1965-07-29; 1965-08-04; Gardner_Sampler_17
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Jim Gunn and Gary White - "Blood Red Roses," "Lamachree and Meagram," "The Moneymusk Lads," "The Mucking of Geordie's Byre," "The Working Chap"; John Pollock and Tommy Thompson - Blues instrumental, "Autobiographical Blues"; Tommy Thompson - "Trouble in Mind"; John Pollack - "Bleeker Street," "Baby Blue," "Green Rocky Road"; Earl Palmer - Instrumental, "Malaguena"; Roger Abrahams from concert at Jewish Community Center on 1963-11-10 - "Roll on Buddy," "Make Me a Pallet," "Ballad of Georgie," "An Old Man," "One Morning in May"
  - The Sampler - Scott Holtzman, Buddy Wigington, Kathy Rote, Frank Davis, Peter Childs, Carolyn Terry, Sarah Wiggins, Jim McConnell, Robin Rinker, 1965-08-02; 1965-08-11; Gardner_Sampler_18
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Scott Holtzman discusses writing songs, "selling" them, writing with Vivian Holtzman on "Maryanne's Magic Castle" and doing a recording for Kay Oslin - "I'm Not Sayin'," Scott Holtzman and Buddy Wigington - "Fair Rosamunds Bower," Scott Holtzman, Buddy Wingington, Robin Rinker - "Early Morning Rain," "Babe I'm Gonna Leave You," "Railroad Wife"; Kathy Rote - "Two LIttle Boys," "Wild Rippling Water"; Frank Davis, Peter Childs, Carolyn Terry, Sarah Wiggins - "Motherless Child"; Sarah Wiggins and Jim McConnell - "Tarry Town"; Jim McConnell and Peter Childs - "Nine Pound Hammer," "Darby Ram," "I Saw the Light," "Somewhere Listening"
  - The Sampler - Guy Clark, Gary White, Carolyn Terry, Tim Reid, Amy Goodenough, Pete Wheeler, Robin Rinker, Kathy Rokte, Pete Seeger, 1965-08-09; 1965-08-18; Gardner_Sampler_19
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Guy Clark and Gary White - "Cripple Creek," "Shady Grove," "Fair and Tender Ladies"; Carolyn Terry - "Silver Dagger," "East Virginia," "Black is the Color"; Tim Reid - "Vandy," "Blue Mountain"; Amy Goodenough - "A Single Life Is / I Wish I Was a Single Girl"; Pete Wheeler - "Trouble on My Mind"; "I Wish I Was a Mole"; Robin Rinker - "Bury Me Beneath the Willow," "Sourwood Mountain"; Gary White and Amy Goodenough - "Willy Moore"; Gary White - "Little Maggie"; Kathy Rote - "Willow Garden," "Old Blue"; Guy Clark - "Devil and Farmer's Wife"; From a recording Pete Seeger - "How Can I Keep from Singing"
  - The Sampler - Gary White, Guy Clark, Danny Schacht, Carolyn Terry, Amy Goodenough, 1965-08-16; 1965-08-25; Gardner_Sampler_20
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Gary White - "Fannin St.," "Winsboro Cotton Mill Blues"; Guy Clark - "San Francisco Bay Blues"; Gary White, Danny Schacht, Guy Clark - "C.C. Rider," "Stealin'"; Danny Schacht - "Betty Dupree," "Questionnaire"; Carolyn Terry - "Blackbird," "Alabama Woman"; Amy Goodenough - "Every Night"; Gary White - "Girl from North Country," "High Flying Bird"; Guy Clark - "Green Rocky Road," "Baby Please Don't Go"; Carolyn Terry - "You've Been a Good Old Wagon," "Blues When You're Lonely"
  - The Sampler - Gary White, Robin Rinker, Jim Gunn, Kathy Rote, Robert Gaston, Amy Goodenough, Pete Seeger, Judy Collins, Clancy Brothers and Tommy Makem, 1965-08-30; 1965-09-08; Gardner_Sampler_22
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Gary White - "Home in That Rock," "This Land," "Paul and Silas"; Robin Rinker - "Lollipop Tree"; Jim Gunn - "Hallelujah I'm a Bum"; Kathy Rote - "Very Unfortunate Man"; Robert Gaston - "Bottle of Wine"; Amy Goodenough - "Jug a' Red," "When I First Came to This Land"; What follows is commercially recorded - Pete Seeger - "Guantenamera," "Tshotsholosa"; Judy Collins - "Ramblin' Boy"; Clancy Brothers and Tommy Makem - "Moonshiner," "Whistlin' Gypsy," "My Johnny Lad," "Work of the Weavers," "The Old Orange Flute," "Brennan on the Moor"
  - The Sampler - Ed Badeaux, John Gatenby, Ewan MacColl, 1965-09-15; Gardner_Sampler_23
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Ed Badeaux - "The Drunk Rat," "Blues Chased a Rabbit," "Talking Beginning Guitar Blues," "Pie in the Sky," "Dark as a Dungeon," "Alberta"; What follows is commercially recorded - John Gatenby - two bagpipe selections; Ewan MacColl - "Green Grow the Rashes," "Rothesay-O," "Carlton Weaver"
  - The Sampler - Carolyn Terry, Frank Davis, Kathy Rote, 1965-09-20; 1965-09-22; Gardner_Sampler_24
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Carolyn Terry hosts. Frank Davis - "Big Fat Woman," "Jean Harlow"; Kathy Rote - "Duncan and Brady"; Kathy Rote and Carolyn Terry - "Ella Speed"; Guy Clark about to embark on a two month long jr. high school tour, replacing Ed Badeaux who became the editor for Sing Out - "I Got Mine," "Everyday Dirt"; Gary White - "Ace in the Hole," "Red Hot Mama," "Man Without a Woman"; Frank Davis - "Nobody Knows You," "Young Man"; Gary White - "How Come You Do Me"; Sarah Wiggins - "Crowded," "Trouble in Mind"; Guy Clark - "No Room" [? title unclear, no chorus] - 1st recorded original song; Carolyn Terry - "Rag Time Life"; What follows is commercially recorded - Leadbelly - "Salty Dog," "Easy Mr. Tom," "Release Your Mind"
  - The Sampler - Robert Gaston, Paul Johnson, Carolyn Terry, Pete Wheeler, Gary White, Frank Davis, Kay Olsin, Lynne Taylor, Gene and Francesca, Cynthia Gooding, Joan Baez, 1965-09-27; 1965-09-29; Gardner_Sampler_25
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Robert Gaston - "Lady and Cowboy"; Paul Johnson - "Last Thing on My Mind," "Golden Apples"; Carolyn Terry - "Marrowbones," "My Love Loves the Game"; Pete Wheeler - "Six Questions," "Equinonial"; Gary White - "Westerin' Wind," "When I Was Single," "The House Carpenter"; What follows is commercially recorded or recorded live by Gardner at an earlier time - "Frank Davis and Kay Oslin - "Rattlesnake Mountain," "My Girl"; Lynne Taylor - "Ha Ha This Way"; Gene and Francesca - "Meu Limao"; Cynthia Gooding - "Aupres de ma Blonde"; Joan Baez - "Rake and Ramblin' Boy"
  - The Sampler - Paul Johnson, Carolyn Terry, Kathy Rote, Paul Johnson, Alex Martin, Gospel Mellowtones, Flatlanders, 1965-10-04; 1965-10-06; Gardner_Sampler_26
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Paul Johnson - "Oh My Lady," "Talkin' Atom"; Carolyn Terry - "Peter Emberly," "Henry Martin"; Kathy Rote - "Cruel Mother," "Me and My Uncle"; Paul Johnson - Instrumental "Prelude et Impromptu," "Turn Around"; Examples of pre-recorded performances at the Jewish Community Center - Alex Martin - "T for Texas," "Streets of Laredo"; Gospel Mellowtones - "I Saw a Beautiful Light," "Oh Mighty God"; Flatlanders - Instrumental, "Bile That Cabbage Down"
  - The Sampler - John Pollack, Sarah Wiggins, Carl Snyder, Bob Gaston, Gary White, Sarah Wiggins, 1965-10-11; 1965-10-13; Gardner_Sampler_27
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. John Pollack - "House of the Rising Sun," "Corinna"; Sarah Wiggins - "One Too Many Mornings," "Ain't No More Cane," "John Anderson My Joe"; Carl Snyder - "Fare Thee Wall," "I Never Will Marry"; Bob Gaston - "Last Thing on My Mind," "Deep River Blues"; Gary White - "To Go to Sea Once More," "One Grain of Sand," "Two Little Sailor Boys," "North Country"; Sarah Wiggins - "Joey," "Daily Growing"
  - The Sampler - Paul Johnson, Louise Ack, Bob Gaston, Robin Rinker, Gary White, Sarah Wiggins, Peter Gardner, Carolyn Terry, Amy Goodenough, Gary White, 1965-10-18; 1965-10-20; Gardner_Sampler_28
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Paul Johnson - "Great Silkie"; Louise Ack - "There Is a Lady," "Lowlands of Holland"; Bob Gaston - "East Virginia," "Little Margaret"; Robin Rinker - "The Cruise of hte Bilge Bucket," "Ah Sid"; Gary White - "Lowland Sea," "Dewie Dens of Yarrow"; Sarah Wiggins - "The Moonshiner," "Fair and Tender Ladies"; Peter Gardner - "20, 18, 16, 14," "I Gave My Love and Apple"; Carolyn Terry - "Frankie Slide"; Amy Goodenough - "The Blacksmith," "Yarrow"; Gary White - "Buddy, Won't You Roll Down the Line," "Few Days"
  - The Sampler - Gary White, Carolyn Terry, Bob Beck, Rick Kelly, Bob Gaston, Gary Whtie, Amy Goodenough, Paul Johnson, 1965-10-25; 1965-10-27; Gardner_Sampler_29
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Gary White - "Midnite Special," "Make Me a Pallet," "Reuben James"; Carolyn Terry - "Me and My Uncle," "Hootenanny Granny"; Bob Beck - "One Meat Ball," "Johnson City Blues," "16 Tons"; Rick Kelly - "Fare Thee Well," "Don't Think Twice"; Bob Gaston - "North Country," "I've Been a Rambler"; Gary White - "Lewis Collins," "Black Girl"; Amy Goodenough - "Soul Song"; Paul Johnson - "Green Grow the Lilacs"
  - The Sampler - The Moonshiners, 1965-10-25; 1965-11-03; Gardner_Sampler_30
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. The Moonshiners - Instrumental opening, "Jimmy Brown, The Newsboy," "The Cuckoo Bird," "Banks of the Ohio," "Wildwood Flower," "Nine Pound Hammer," "Salty Dog Blues," "Under the Double Eagle," "Take the Hammer," "Ain't Gonna Rain No More," "Froggy Mountain Breakdown," "Goodbye, Mary Dear," "Reuben James," "The Froggy Mountain Top," "Weeping Willow," "The Cumberland Gap," "I Wonder How the Old Folks Are at Home," "Mountain Dew," "Little Maggie," Instrumental closing. Musicians: Gary White, Robbie Shipley, Bill Bailey, Bill Bonner
  - The Sampler - Gary White, Bob Beck, Minor Wilson, Nancy Storm, Carl Snyder, Minor Wilson, Sarah Wiggins, Gary White, 1965-11-10; Gardner_Sampler_31
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Gary White - "Bullgine Run," "William Morgan," "Hills of Rome County"; Bob Beck - "I Just Lover Her So," "San Francisco Bay Blues"; Minor Wilson - "Old Tom Cat Blues," "Blues Came Back"; Nancy Storm - "Hi Ro Jerum," "Houseman Song"; Carl Snyder - "I'm Going Back"; Minor Wilson - Blues Before Sunrise," "Black Mountain"; Sarah Wiggins - "There's a Hill," "The First Time," "The Cuckoo"; Gary White - "The Engineer's Lament," "Wreck on the Highway," "Empy Pocket Blues"
  - The Sampler - Bill Northcutt, Gary White, Susan Spaw, Paul Johnson, Amy Goodenough, Sarah Wiggins, 1965-11-17; Gardner_Sampler_32
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Bill Northcutt and Gary White - "I Truly Understand," "Old Mother Hare," "Mary Deare"; Susan Spaw - "Old Blue," "Where I'm Bound," "Polly Von"; Paul Johnson and Amy Goodenough - "Rocks and Gravel," "Winken and Blinken and Nod"; Amy Goodenough - "Joe Hill's Epitaph," "Pastures of Plenty"; Paul Johnson - "Amanda Blaine," "Shelby Flint Song," "Crow in the Cradle"; Sara Wiggins - "The Fox," "If I'd a Known," "Black Girl"; Bill Northcutt and Gary White - "Dixie"
  - The Sampler - Gary White, Sarah Wiggins, Ken Roberts, Bob Gaston, Carolyn Terry, 1965-11-22; 1965-11-24; Gardner_Sampler_33
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Gary White and Sarah Wiggins - "Gonna Miss Me When I'm Gone," "Four Strong Winds," "One Too Many Mornings"; Ken Roberts - "North Country," "Samson," "Strange Fruit," "Don't Think Twice"; Bob Gaston - "Ginger Man," "Panama Limited"; Carolyn Terry - "Song for Canada," "Shake Sugaree"; Gary White - "My Name is Morgan," "Make Me a Pallet"
  - The Sampler - Jim McConnell, Amy Goodenough, Jim Gunn, Susan Spaw, Gary White, Paul Johnson, 1965-11-29; 1965-12-01; Gardner_Sampler_34
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Jim McConnell - "Stagolee," "Sheep Shearing"; Amy Goodenough - "Scarborough Fair," "Grey Cock"; Jim Gunn - "On Monday Morning," "Brewer Laddie," "Lamachree Megram," "The Moneymusk Lads"; Susan Spaw - "Wake Up This Morning," "Shennandoah"; Gary White - "Bow and Balance," "The Royal Canal," Paul Johnson - "I'm a Drifter," "Coal Town Road"; Amy Goodenough - "Cotton Mill Girls"; Jim McConnell - "Darby Ram"
  - The Sampler - Gary White, Kathy Rote, Pete Wheeler, Guy Clark, Susan Spaw, Paul Johnson, 1965-12-06; 1965-12-08; Gardner_Sampler_35
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Gary White - "Everyday Dirt," "Tim Evans"; Kathy Rote - "Red Velvet," "Losin' Blues," "Early in the Spring"; Pete Wheeler - "The Cambric Shirt," "The Three Tailors"; Guy Clark - "One Too Many Mornings," "Frankie and Johnny," "Spider to a Fly," "Early Morning Rain"; Susan Spaw - "John Riley"; Paul Johnson - "Winter Sky"; Guy Clark - "Silver Dagger," "I Got Mine"
  - The Sampler - Carolyn Terry, Don Evans, Bob Gaston, Robin Rinker, Dickenson Glee and Mandolin Society, Tom Reid, Townes Van Zandt, 1965-12-13; 1965-12-15; Gardner_Sampler_36
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Carolyn Terry - "Oh My Darlin' Oh," "Little Maggie"; Don Evans - "Shennandoah," "Wayfarin' Stranger," "Red Rosy Bush"; Bob Gaston - "In the Morning," "Long John Gone"; Robin Rinker - "Marvelous Toy," "All on a Christmas Day"; Dickenson Glee and Mandolin Society - "Will the Circle Be Unbroken," "Tom Dooley," "Amelia Earhart"; Tom Reid - "Fennario"; Townes Van Zandt - "Big Country Blues," "Minneapolis Hotel," "Waitin' around to Die"
  - The Sampler - Gary White, Sarah Wiggins, Paul Johnson, Ron Hudson, Carolyn Terry, Susan Spaw, Amy Goodenough, 1965-12-20; 1965-12-22; Gardner_Sampler_37
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Gary White - Instrumental carols, "Virgin Mary Had a Baby," "Poor LIttle Jesus"; Sarah Wiggins - "I Wander as I Wander"; Paul Johnson - "Mary's Boy Child"; Paul Johnson and Amy Goodenough - "All Through the Night"; Ron Hudson - "Ave Maria"; Carolyn Terry - "Cherry Tree Carol"; Susan Spaw - "I Saw Three Ships"; Amy Goodenough - "Birthdays Are Funny Things"; Gary White and Paul Johnson - instrumental, "Soul Cake"; Gary White - "Virgin Mary," "Go Where I Send Thee," "We Wish You a Merry Christmas"; Group - "Twelves Days of Christmas," "Santa Claus is Comin' to Town," "Go Tell It on the Mountain," medley of carols
  - The Sampler - The Moonshiners, Gary White, Amy Goodenough, Carolyn Terry, Kathy Rote, Jim Gunn, Guy Clark, 1965; Gardner_Sampler_49
    Contents include: The Moonshiners - "Mountain Dew"; Gary White, Amy Goodenough, Earl, Carolyn Terry - "Haul Away Joe"; Amy Goodenough - "The Blacksmith"; Gary White - "Wild Colonial Boy"; Kathy Rote - "Me and My Uncle"; Jim Gunn and Gary White - "Ranzo the Boys"; Guy Clark - "Tying a Knot on the Devil's Tail," "London Town" aka "Handsom Molly"; Carolyn Terry and Gary White - "The Vanquished Grave"; Carolyn Terry and Gary White - "The Jealous Lover"; Group sing-along - "Weary Bones"
  - The Sampler - Bob Gaston, Beverly Wehking, Townes Van Zandt, Carolyn Terry, Carl Snyder, Jerry Jeff Walker, 1966-01-03; 1966-01-05; Gardner_Sampler_38
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Bob Gaston - "Corinna"; Beverly Wehking - "It Ain't Me," "Melorna's Lullaby," "I Have No Song"; Townes Van Zandt - "Today Was a Time" original, "Trouble in Mind," "To My Friend That's Gone Along His Way" [?] - original song - playing at the Beaumont Halfway House on 01/15-01/16 and 01/22-01/23; Carolyn Terry - "Gilderoy," "Moonshiner"; Carl Snyder - "Harvest Song," "Lord Henry," "Jamaica Farewell"; Jerry Jeff Walker - "Roads of My Mind," "Ramblin', Scramblin'"
  - The Sampler - Amy Goodenough, John A. Lomax, Jr., Susan Spaw, Paul Johnson, Jerry Jeff Walker, 1966-01-10; 1966-01-12; Gardner_Sampler_39
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Amy Goodenough - "Blues" original, "As I Went Out"; John A. Lomax, Jr. - "Alabama Bound," "Lulu," "Darlin' Corey," "Gal I Left Behind Me," "Roseanna," "Long John," "Chisholm Trail"; Susan Spaw - "Bells of Rhymney"; Bob Gaston - "Colours," "Long John" replaced the Townes Van Zandt songs - "Talking KKK Blues," "It's Been a Year Now"; Paul Johnson - "Heather on the Hill," "Gimme That Wine"; Paul Johnson and Amy Goodenough - "Song
  - The Sampler - Lynchburg Ferry Old Time String Band and Patent Medicine Co., Kathy Rote, Joe Johnson, Pete Troutner, Pete Wheeler, 1966-01-17; 1966-01-19; Gardner_Sampler_40
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Lynchburg Ferry Old Time String Band and Patent Medicine Co. - "Amelia Earhart's Last Flight," "Take a Drink on Me," "Lightning Express," "Bill Morgan"; Kathy Rote and Joe Johnson - "When First unto This Country," "The Daughter of Dundee," "Ella Speed"; Pete Troutner - "Hello Central," "Buck Dancer's Choice"; Pete Wheeler - "Invery," "Old Man on the Hill"; Lynchburg Ferry Old Time String Band and Patent Medicine Co. - "Man of Constant Sorrow," "I Truly Understand," "Engineer's Last Ride," "Old Account Was Settled," "Mary of the Wild Moor." Lynchburg Ferry Old Time String Band and Patent Medicine Co. musicians - Gary White, Bill Northcutt, Joe Johnson